const quizData = [
  {
    question: "UI Design is _____ practice",
    options: ["Digital", "Local", "Mechanical", "Electronic"],
    correctAnswer: "Digital",
  },
  {
    question: "UI Design can be done with all of the following except",
    options: ["Pens and Pencils", "Computer Visualisation", "Built in Codes", "Python"],
    correctAnswer: "Python",
  },
  {
    question: "UI designers are responsible for maing UX designers vision a reality",
    options: ["True", "False", "Not sure", "I do not know"],
    correctAnswer: "True",
  },
  {
    question: "A good user interface should have all the following except",
    options: ["Responsive", "Attractive", "Clear", "Irregular"],
    correctAnswer: "Irregular",
  },
  {
    question: "Good doors that does not indicate which side to push or pull is",
    options: ["Good User Experience", "Good User Interface", "Bad User Experience", "Bad User Interface"],
    correctAnswer: "Bad User Experience",
  },
  {
    question: "How the user feels when using a product is the repsonsibility of",
    options: ["UI Designer", "UX Designer", "Product Designer", "Graphics Desginer"],
    correctAnswer: "UX Designer",
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following is the first thing to do during user research",
    options: ["Empathy Map", "User Story", "Interview", "Ideation"],
    correctAnswer: "Interview",
  },
  {
    question: "During Figma design, icons can be gotten from",
    options: ["Template", "Plugins", "Downloads", "Preferences"],
    correctAnswer: "Plugins",
  },
  {
    question: "The last phase of a UI/UX design project is",
    options: ["User Research", "Prototyping", "Wireframe", "User Testing"],
    correctAnswer: "User Testing",
  },
  {
    question: "The last phase of a UX design project is",
    options: ["User Research", "User Flow", "Wireframe", "User Testing"],
    correctAnswer: "User Flow",
  },
  {
    question: "The first phase of a UI design project is",
    options: ["Hi-Fi", "Prototyping", "Wireframe", "Lo-Fi"],
    correctAnswer: "Wireframe",
  },
  {
    question: "During design on Figma, the shortcut to copy object is to",
    options: ["Ctrl+D", "Ctrl+C", "Alt+Left Drag mouse", "Ctrl+Alt"],
    correctAnswer: "Alt+Left Drag mouse",
  },
  {
    question: "During design on Figma, the shortcut for Frame is",
    options: ["Ctrl+F", "F", "Ctrl+R", "R"],
    correctAnswer: "F",
  },
  {
    question: "Figjam is a tool for",
    options: ["UI design", "UX design", "Graphics design", "Front end dev"],
    correctAnswer: "UX design",
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following is NOT on the Empathy Map",
    options: ["Feel", "Think", "Say", "Idea"],
    correctAnswer: "Idea",
  },
  {
    question: "The shortcut key to use Auto Layout is",
    options: ["Shift+A", "Ctrl+A", "Alt+A", "Fn+A"],
    correctAnswer: "Shift+A",
  },
  {
    question: "Figma is preferred over other UI design tool because",
    options: ["It is easy to use", "It is a collaborative tool", "It does not consume internet data", "It has an App"],
    correctAnswer: "It is a collaborative tool",
  },
  {
    question: "On User Flow, Circle shape indicates",
    options: ["Start", "Action", "Decision", "Process"],
    correctAnswer: "Action",
  },
  {
    question: "On User Flow, Diamond shape indicates?",
    options: ["Start", "Action", "Decision", "Process"],
    correctAnswer: "Decison",
  },
  {
    question: "The graphical skeleton of a UI design is",
    options: ["Wireframe", "Lo-Fi", "Hi-Fi", "Prototype"],
    correctAnswer: "Wireframe",
  },
  {
    question: "Wireframe design uses all the following except",
    options: ["Lines", "Box", "Colour", "Grayscale colour"],
    correctAnswer: "Colour",
  },
  {
    question: "The dynamic display of a UI/UX design is called",
    options: ["Prototyping", "Brainstorming", "Typography", "Colour Theory"],
    correctAnswer: "Prototyping",
  },
  {
    question: "When designing on Figma, after choosing a frame, the best practice is to start by",
    options: ["Creating a Column", "Creating a Grid", "Draw a container", "Expand your frame"],
    correctAnswer: "Creating a Column",
  },
  {
    question: "Icons to be used in Figma designs are best gotten from",
    options: ["Google", "Figma community", "Other people works", "Preferences"],
    correctAnswer: "Figma community",
  },
  {
    question: "The white space between the column on Figma design is called",
    options: ["Columns", "Rows", "Stroke", "Gutters"],
    correctAnswer: "Gutters",
  },
  {
    question: "To save your project on Figma, is to",
    options: ["Ctrl+S", "Connect to the internet and Synchronize", "Restart the browser", "Restart the Sysytem"],
    correctAnswer: "Connect to the internet and Synchronize",
  },
  {
    question: "Designs can be exported using the following file format except",
    options: ["jpeg", "png", "svg", "pdf"],
    correctAnswer: "svg",
  },
  {
    question: "The simple formula to write a good User Story invloves all except",
    options: ["Types of User", "Action", "Benefit", "Pain Point"],
    correctAnswer: "Pain Point",
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following User Story is complete?",
    options: ["I want high quality tools so I can create desirable works of art",
      "As a team manager, I want to streamline administrative processes so that my employees remain productive",
      "As a teache, I want access to  more reading resouces for my students", "None of the above"],
    correctAnswer: "As a team manager, I want to streamline administrative processes so that my employees remain productive"
  },
  {
    question: "On User Flow, which shape represent backward direction",
    options: ["Lines with arrow", "Dotted lines", "Rectangle", "Circle"],
    correctAnswer: "Dotted Lines",
  },
  {
    question: "On the Idea Prioritization Matrix, what action is to be take for High Effort and Low Value",
    options: ["Do Now", "Do Next", "Do Later", "Do not do"],
    correctAnswer: "Do not do",
  },
  {
    question: "A research plan consists of the following except",
    options: ["Empathy Map", "Interview Script", "Research Objectives", "List of Participant"],
    correctAnswer: "Empathy Map",
  },
  {
    question: "On the Idea Prioritization Matrix, what action is to be take for Low Effort and High Value",
    options: ["Do Now", "Do Next", "Do Later", "Do not do"],
    correctAnswer: "Do Now",
  },
  {
    question: "On the Idea Prioritization Matrix, what action is to be take for High Effort and High Value",
    options: ["Do Now", "Do Next", "Do Later", "Do not do"],
    correctAnswer: "Do Next",
  },
  {
    question: "On the Idea Prioritization Matrix, what action is to be take for Low Effort and Low Value",
    options: ["Do Now", "Do Next", "Do Later", "Do not do"],
    correctAnswer: "Do Later",
  },
  {
    question: "The research that takes place during the design process is called?",
    options: ["Foundation research", "Design research", "Launch research", "Post-Launch research"],
    correctAnswer: "Design research",
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following is NOT a quality of a good researcher",
    options: ["Sympathy", "Empathy", "Collaboration", "Pregmatic"],
    correctAnswer: "Sympathy",
  },
  {
    question: "During Ideation, which of the following practice is NOT suitable",
    options: [
      "Pick one pain point at a time and come up with “how might we” questions in order to see room for solutions",
      "Do not limit the range of your ideas",
      "Aim for quality over quanity",
      "Document all the ideas you come up with"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Aim for quality over quanity",
  },
  {
    question: "Which shape indicate Action on a user flow",
    options: ["Circle", "Rectangle", "Diamond", "Line"],
    correctAnswer: "Circle",
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following is NOT a design best practice?",
    options: ["Creating style guides",
      "Renaming design frames",
      "Expanding the width of a design frame to fit desired content",
      "Setting out a layout grid on a frame"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Expanding the width of a design frame to fit desired content",
  },
]
export default quizData;